insanehomefatloss.com 2015-12-30

# INSANE HOME FAT LOSS

You can opt-out of all email contact from us by using our [email unsubscribe page](http://app.icontact.com/icp/mmail-mprofile.pl?r=82992&l=106&s=GXBQ&m=59770&c=906767). We will only call you if you're a customer and there's a problem with your account or order -- but if you'd also like to opt-out of phone contact, you can do that through our [phone contact opt-out page](http://sixpackshortcuts.com/phone_optout.php). 

**What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you register on our site or subscribe to our newsletter. 

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, phone number or credit card information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

* * *

**What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

• To improve our website  
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)

• To improve customer service  
(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)

• To process transactions

> Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.

* * *

**How do we protect your information?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information. 

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to?keep the information confidential.

After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be kept on file for more than 60 days.

* * *

**Do we use cookies?**

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

* * *

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

* * *

**Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

* * *

**Online Privacy Policy Only**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

* * *

**Re-Marketing Cookies And Information Collection**   
When you visit SixPackShortcuts.com, MikeChangFitness.com, insanehomefatloss.com, our YouTube channel, or any of our other sites you may be tagged with a "re-marketing" cookie. We use this technology with our advertising partners to serve you relevant, useful and helpful ads.   
**Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our [privacy policy](http://www.freeprivacypolicy.com/).

* * *

**Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below. 

http://www.insanehomefatloss.com  
Six Pack Shortcuts  
9111A Research Blvd.  
Austin, TX 78758  
USA  
mike@sixpackshortcuts.com

### **1(800) 655-8576**

if you calling within the US or 

### **512-201-4646**

for outside of the US.
